{
    "subject": "resource/Dorothy_Appleby",
    "predicate": "property/yearsActive",
    "object": "1931",
    "human_readable": "Dorothy Appleby was active from 1931.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9225760102272034,
            "question": "When was Dorothy Appleby active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7146204113960266,
            "question": "What were some of the significant events happening during Dorothy Appleby's active period?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6728141903877258,
            "question": "What was Dorothy Appleby known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6321274042129517,
            "question": "Was Dorothy Appleby a notable figure in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.462934672832489,
            "question": "Can you find any information about Dorothy Appleby's life beyond her activity period?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3689817190170288,
            "question": "In what field did Dorothy Appleby likely work or contribute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3472770154476166,
            "question": "Were there any notable people or events that intersected with Dorothy Appleby's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3347924053668976,
            "question": "What impact might Dorothy Appleby have had on her field of work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21128158271312714,
            "question": "Are there any primary sources or documents related to Dorothy Appleby's life and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2108519822359085,
            "question": "How can we learn more about Dorothy Appleby's contributions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dorothy Appleby was active from 1931.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4863_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any primary sources or documents related to Dorothy Appleby's life and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4863_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact might Dorothy Appleby have had on her field of work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4863_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable people or events that intersected with Dorothy Appleby's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4863_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4863_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Dorothy Appleby was active from 1931, as it is mentioned in multiple places (e.g., \"...She appeared in over 50 films between 1931 and 1943.\") that she appeared in films during this time period."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Dorothy Appleby was active from 1931.\" Specifically, it mentions that she appeared in over 50 films between 1931 and 1943."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}